arrowpress.net 2019-01-19

# Privacy policy - Premium WordPress themes

At ArrowPress, we reckon that privacy is important and we are committed to protecting your privacy. This policy describes how we collect, store, use and protect your personal information. Our policy is assumed to be accepted when you register and use our services.

Which information is collected:

When you visit Arrowpress.net, we will collect your IP address and web browser information. If you create an account at arrowpress.net, you are required to provide your personal information including name, address, valid email address. Once you place orders at our store, you will be asked to give us some more information suchs as shipping/ billing address, phone, company…

How we use your information

Our main aim to collect your personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth and efficient environment as you browse our website. We use this information to process and deliver your order and to provide an excellent personal shopping experience. Moreover, we will be able to communicate with you about orders and promotional updates later on. You can view and edit your personal information at any time by logging into your account and go to the My Account section.

How we use cookies

When you visit our site, we may place small data files called “cookies” on your computer. This information contains information about you, and it helps us to recognize you if you visit multiple pages on our site in the same session without you having to enter password on each page. When you log out your account or close your browser, this cookie expires and no longer has any effect. If you disable cookies for our site, you can still surf our site, but certain benefits of shopping experiences with us may be affeced.

AdWords remarketing is a market behavior and target service provided by Google. It connects arrowpress.net activities with networks of AdWords advertisers. You can opt-out cookie track here. Personal data collected: Cookie and user data.

How we protect and store personal information

We are committed to protecting personal information strictly. We store your information on a secure server. We use SSL for the checkout process to help you keep your payment information securely. No credit card information stored on our system. We do not share your personal information with any other third parties.

Changes to this privacy policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. ArrowPress reserves rights to amend this Privacy Policy at any time. We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy on this page and if the changes are remarkable, we will provide a more prominent notice.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at any time via website, phone or email.
